Your uniform caught my eye, boss.   Don't just [ __ ]
this up.  I am blessed to have this opportunity
.   No need
.
Boss, go and have a drink and eat,
boss.  I'll make it happen.  Yes,
sister,
look at your work. I'm just
asking about work.
Go and sleep,
that's all you gave me.
This guy who threw the ball
was probably a master at the Proto shop before this.   It seems like there's a
lot of monkey pranks going on, so you have to be
a little careful
.
[Sigh]
What's wrong, Karukana? What
happened to him?
Oh my God,
who would do this? Show me before my eyes. Oh my God.
[Screaming]
Who is this? I will put
an end to your troubles.
Why did the earth go like this?
Father, [Screaming] Save it, save it, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, save the
earth. Don't stop. Is this the
time to play with the moon?
I fought with my mother. This is the one who took the
box and fired it.
Look how it fired. Look,
everyone. You don't need
a place to keep it warm. You
ugly bastard.
This is not a place to show girls.
What did I do? I showed you. I showed you the douchebag. I didn't do anything. I was lying there thinking, "What's wrong?" I took
that
pot and boiled it. It's boiling. I didn't do
anything.
I told you, no, I don't
want to do anything.  I didn't want to do it, so
why did I do it like this?
Look how he did it. Look, he wanted to put a goat in it. It's not
even okay. He made a hole like this and
did it without helping anything. Idiot,
yes, idiot. Who made the hole in this?
I want to know right now. It's
you.
How can I make this dog run here while I'm asleep?
Sovannabulis
[screaming]
Boss, take me alone and pinch me and tear me apart. I'll
take it willingly.  But
why are you talking so rudely in front of the doll?
You and I are
forced to go to Anonion.
Somana, Puli Samna, I have enough of this sleeping
sickness. I have enough of this. I
have burned a pair of pants
. This is such a protest.  What should I wear to college tomorrow
?
Why would you put this?
Don't you have another lice shirt?   Is
this my uniform?   What kind of
LKG student are you to wear a uniform
?
Ask me that.
What's the point of studying all the big LKGs?
The next guy bought an iron pack from Medex and
read that it was safe to store.  This is not the case
.
Turn off the lights and go to bed.
Today's uniform is a must.   I'm not
looking for
another iron box, boss.
Another ion box,
look here, there are two, there is only one ion box, look where, look, he has this in his mouth, look, what is it, wait
Look at this, if she
likes you, she will definitely come looking for you
.
Excuse Me
[Music]
You said it was Profactor's, it's like a dance studio
.  Factory, our profession,
dance, our fashion,
oh nice, so you'll do all the shows
?
Oh, we are very famous here, this Tamil
dance team, have you heard of
anything like that?
[Laughter]
What, you came all this way to see what I was
saying, I did
n't come to see you, I
came to see you.
Okay, okay, that's it.
Excuse me, tell me what's wrong?
We are opening the restaurant tomorrow.  That's why
Dad told me to invite all the suppliers
.  Come here, and definitely
come here without eating.
Why are you going to do blood tests on everyone tomorrow
?
Oh no, breakfast is okay, come here,
you too.
[Music]
Bro, she didn't come to see you, she invited you, what did she come to see on the pretext of that? Yes, she invited you, you went and
saw her, she gave you juice and coffee.
What if there were people who gave you tea and coffee? Bro, for love,
even a brick will be served, I will
eat it.
You eat that, why should I?
You should eat too.  Because
you are my bro.   Is
everything ready?   Come and
taste it when it's ready.
[Laughter]
What is this?
Yogurt rice.  [Laughter]
What's this blackness, if it's salty?
No problem.  Guru, you are
very wrong.  How did
you come to run a hotel without knowing all this?  I don't
understand anything.   Was
n't it wrong for me to come and run a hotel?   Look, he's the one who's trying to be
like you,
that's his mistake.
Follow me.
Sir, I asked for the color of the couch.
Put some here, this is a
great meal [laughter]
I'll come over here to buy some
[laughter] Does
anyone want the last spoon?
This one wants it. Is there
a hospital nearby within
walking distance? I was just waiting for the trouble to come and go
.  Eat the third side
.  Oh, do
n't worry, brother, I'll make you a colorful
variety tomorrow.
We will come back tomorrow.
We will come tomorrow.
[Laughter]
Does the donkey know?   The
camphor scent is so strong that you can't even cook it
.   You should
have cut off your hand for cooking like this.  It was a
mistake to tie it.
[Laughter]
Hi Meera,
Hi Vishwa,
what's up Meera? Tell me,
what's wrong, you don't like to eat anything
?  [Laughter]
No, no, I just drink coffee in the morning
.  Did your
friends like everything they ate
?
Meera asks how the meal was
.
Tell me it was great.   If it's
great, will you come daily?
[Sigh]
Thank you.
I told you when, bro.
That's it. Hello, hello,
hello.
Say
something. I'm sorry, my
dear. Can
you
join our dance team?
Thank you,
thank you, thank you, I can
come and buy it. Does
Meera really like dancing?
They want to join our dance team.  You're the only one who doesn't like dancing
.
Dad doesn't like it, Dad won't come.
Both are the same.
My delicious
side dish is always fresh.
Side dish, this is a pest control, it's a pest
control.  This is easy, what kind of mint
chutney is this? Did you think Aralli would come and chop it up?
You have to mix both and then put it away.   I've been
telling you this for three hours, and
he's just
showing off his tricks.
Okay, why this decision, my dear?   I
don't know, I don't know, I
don't even know how to make love [laughter]?   I
know.
He is getting married tomorrow morning at 9:00
.  I don't know if that's the case.
Her
father is in the newspaper, but he's the
only one who's been there. Do you
think that if I go, Shanti will be happy? She'll
drink something like that and leave
. Then they'll say that marriage is in heaven. What's the point of having so many friends? If it was like this, our father would have left her like this. What is it? Is he drinking poison now? Poison.
The wedding will take place tomorrow.  They will fall at
your feet and beg you, groom, to marry my daughter
.
How how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how how to do a
letter to my dear father
your son kadhiresan write to my dear father
i love a girl named garbhagam
I have told you many times.
You
did not agree to our marriage.
I have no interest in this marriage at all.  So
I'm leaving this town with my girlfriend and going to a
place out of sight.  Don't look for me
.  Did you hear?  Did this groom
run away to a place where he could not be seen?  Did he run away
?
Oh my goodness, someone must have looked up and
found out where I am.
Oh, wait.   Made a
noise.  If the groom runs away,
your life will be like this.
You won't faint.  What a charm, what a charm.
Oh my, the bride
has arrived.
Who will marry this girl now?
How do you build it?
Someone here is going to make a big man out of you and marry you off
.
How is that?  Even if the kathirika doesn't come, if one
property is changed,
who here has such a great man?  It won't happen, it won't happen
.
Why won't it happen? I'm getting married
.   I am not me
.  This person
will get married to this person.
Sir, are you getting married?
I did a little build-up, which Bhudevi didn't immediately agree to.
What kind of comedy are you doing?
Suddenly, a girl is getting married
.  How come you told me to spice it up
?
You shouldn't say that, sir.   Are
you the one who is building up the marriage? Ca
n't you get married?
Look at that girl's face, sir.
You're the one who should get married somehow,
sir.   You ca
n't just marry someone who looks at you from the front and back, can you?   Hey
brother, I'm also watching
.  How long have you been
talking to each other about the song?
How long has that brother been begging?   Please
speak a little bit more politely.
Brother, you've gone to such lengths to speak for that girl
.  Hey, are you her brother?
What are you asking me like this for? I
was just born, bro?
Oh my god, you're like a dagger, don't you think?
That brother, who is your son,
is fighting for your daughter. You're
like a check, go and tell that boy to tie the knot with the
girl. Even if
the gift falls, it doesn't
matter. Oh, just leave it alone. Just leave it alone. Don't let that
girl get hurt. May
our blessings be upon her.
This wedding happened because of my brother.
[Laughter] Blessings to my brother.
This marriage is a disgrace because of this
brother.   I would like to
say that he is a very good brother and a good friend
.
Did you know that we went to the movie the other day? I really liked that movie.   Be
brave, my dear.
That too, the heroine is first and foremost.
I really like it.
My friend is waiting for his Plus Two results
.   Okay, okay
.  493
What, what
No, brother [laughter] My friend made our rava pass, so I'll
see you by the sea for 10 days.
That's why
I told them I found it in the water, so I tried to find another job
.  I got a job, I got it, I was the one who wanted to be old
.
Why don't you
give me a job to sweat,
how do we get rid of it?
How can we even say that we found something in the water and then turn it into a bathing water?
That water is different from this water. There
is no difference between the two.
So you're just eating and hanging around without doing any work
.   You ca
n't say that so bluntly.  Let
me give you a guess.
Who is it?
[Music] Stuck, stuck
Which one?  [Music] Is
she wearing makeup? Maybe she
's an actress?
Yes, yes, the actress is the actress,
what is her name?
KR Vijaya, who is KR
Vijaya? We haven't seen the previous Punna, the latest, the latest,
then the remake,
oh my head is so smooth, it's getting a little bit
better.
What kind of castile smell do you smell in the middle of this Karuvattu?
We all have to have a
nose for that.
Hey,
why do
normal people
only have warts on their tongues?   Only
fools have nasal discharge
.
Oh
my, what is that girl looking at?
Sura, is that girl watching us?   Do
n't come and look at us, Ambarala, I'm
looking at you.
What are you waiting for?  Are you looking at me
?   Do all these
girls who are fair-skinned
get a bit crazy when they see black guys?
What are you saying, crazy person?  Oh my gosh, then
another important thing.  You shouldn't be so heartbroken and start shaving your beard when that girl
suddenly comes up to me and says, "I love you," and
kisses me
.
[Laughter]
I thought you spat right there. [Music] You came,
what the hell? You came straight like this and
made a U-turn and left. I'm not good at it
.  Oh, he turns like that
.
Oh, sea mummy.  Oh dear.
Oh mother of the sea, what is this shameful thing that I have to say? If I
come to tell you, I will die
in the sea.   Just
leave two.
Ayyappa, don't play around and save that girl. Look at
what kind of young man is this who has sex with a girl.
Hey, web hosting.
You can make a web whenever you want.  But do
you want to prevent a girl's suicide?  It should be like this
ice cream cone.
Go and get it.
Hey hey, listen to this girl.
I'd rather die than anything.  I ca
n't live without my Ramesh.
Oh, love failure, oh my.
No, leave it alone.  I can't live without my Ramesh
.
What if there is no Ramesh, there is a Suresh.   If
there is no Suresh, there is a Dinesh, if there is no Dinesh, there is
a Ganesh, come on.   I ca
n't change my mind like that.  I don't want a life without Ramesh
.  What the hell.
[Music] He
took that boy and went to the water
.   If
you come,
what's up?
Hello, girl,
why didn't you write it? Oh, my God, I'm sorry.
What kind of exhibition are they showing here?
Who's calling the ambulance?
[Music]
First aid for the children in the ambulance,
brother, first aid, brother. How is that? People who
fall into the sea like this
drink a lot of water. So, press your
hand on your stomach like this. Press it. Press it. Press it. Press it. If you keep pressing it like this, will the
intestines come
out through your mouth? Tell me. If you keep
pressing it like this, will
all the water you drank come out through your mouth? Press it.
Brother.
[Music] I'm
very shy. Go. I'm on
duty. You shouldn't be shy after you've been on duty.   Don't be shy,
brother
.
Yes, Raja,
okay, you're telling me, Periyavangallam, let's do it
.
[Music]
Excuse me,
what is it?
Can I have a subconscious brand that I want to have a part in this sacred thing?
Okay, I'll cover the right area
.  Thank you for covering the left area
.
[Music]
What are you two going to do?
What is this, drinking water, to get rid of the water that is in your stomach?  [Laughter] No, it's okay. I'm not going to give you
first aid. But the shoes are still there, and they're
like they're going to sting.
What's the first aid again?
Hey, what's the point of saving me? I
listened to you and saved me.
I don't need this ugliness.
Hey mister, talk to me.
Dad, don't read
this again, I'll pick it up and
throw it back into the sea.
Hey, Big Big,
Hey, do you have any sense? You can't even
get into the house through the door that you're jumping into like this
?
We are all Superman.  This is how
we will arrive.  Hey, what's with the rice bag? I'll
tell your brother to call all these birds and ask them to come to my room
.  Look,
these are all my friends who don't do this kind of insulting stuff.
What is this quarter ticket or half ticket,
your friend?  [Laughter]
Go outside.
Hey, why should I go outside?
I have equal rights in this room.  Dad
told me.
What's up, a full three-foot high, that's the rights issue.
Now go and see,
Sachin Tendulkar has come to the next street. I didn't even
get an autograph from him,
not even a good shirt.
Push it all away and it will all fall apart.  This is a
different toy.
Anna, Sachin is really here,
Sachin is here, and his sister
Aishwarya Rai is here, and
they are shooting an ad film on the next street.
Both of them
disappeared like Vinnal.
Where is he?
Who is he?
In the economy of
Japan, the economy of Japan is the
best economy. In the economy of Japan, the economy of Japan is the best economy. In the economy of Japan
[laughter] Police Part 2 Did you pick a
fight on the street and
come here and study like a good kid
?  My
sister-in-law, my police, my mom.
This is not a police station.  Our house.
Since 6 o'clock in the morning, he has been sitting in his room,
studying sincerely
.  He goes to
Indian Economy [laughter] It's always
his economy. The
first boy in this world to tie a skirt and study will be your boy
.   Did
you think about it and tie a skirt and then, in your
eagerness to study, you did
n't recognize
it?   Don't
believe anything he says, you liar.  He just
jumped in from above a while ago
.
You've come like a curry to my train engine
.   Is it
all his work?
Do you know that Sachin and Aishwarya Rai left us wandering around the streets, saying they were shooting?
I didn't say that, but
Sachidananda Swamiji has
come to the temple next door.  I told him that if he went and
received blessings, he would find wealth
.   What if
you,
knowing that Sachin, took the player and
went looking for Aishwarya Rai, how would you feel
?  As Vadivel says,
there is a small treasure.  Look, Dad.
Hey, I'm just
waiting for you to write all four Aryan papers and pass.
That won't happen. You
keep studying. He'll tell you, "Kabaddi, Kabaddi."
Dad, I forgot all that a long time ago. If you don't believe me,
ask your mother.
Yes, no,
my dear. I'm the one who
talks a lot.  Did you go to Seppiya's house and
play?
Your father is not around,
what do I say? Just feed him.
Your father also
buys every dinosaur for revenge. Uncle, you are not a cow today.
Your father has confused everyone at the party
.  Vijayakanth thinks he has great mental strength
.  I'm
telling you, think about it, Velu.
But your father is very much a policeman
.   We have been
following 24 Hourza for real
.  How are you coping at home
?   Don't
talk to that guy and make him do something else.
Alas!
Hey aunty, you've been asking me a question for a long time, and
you're answering it respectfully.   Does
your father only
put porridge on his dress?  Will the four lots at home
die?  Why are you
looking so different?   He's going to be gone for
a day.
Dude, you
forgot what I was talking about.  "Sachi, do it again,
Kada Kumara has another fever and
is getting worse."
Then, in our village, Duveel Kuppam,
his mother was arrested by the police for a liquor case
.
He said, "Don't worry, I'm
terrible at the match, leave the culture behind."   What happens in
tomorrow's match, brother,
is entirely in your hands.
He's going to have a terrible time buying from us, isn't he?
Dad, he's the wrong number, the
wrong number, the wrong friends.  I can proudly say that my
son is a Tendulkar in cricket and
an Anand in chess.
It seems that Poruki and Pasanga are also playing kabaddi together.  Friends' names are not good,
Kumar is a big dick, they are
talking about a Discovery Channel, what is its name,
I am the only one who is a fox, it has been cut, nothing else,
uncle, tomorrow
morning at 11 am, the Ambedkar round
match, you are asking to come and play.  Kabaddi Kabaddi
Kabaddi Uncle, just like that, you
put that foot in your mouth, you're a rascal, Arnold, I'm
your father, I'm talking to you.
I am your father, but if I
get hold of you, I will kill you,
Raja,
why are you so angry? Tomorrow morning at 11 am,
Kabaddi at Ambedkar Ground
. This is your last warning.
Write all four papers properly, pass them, and then
look for a responsible job.  Hey,
he shouldn't leave the house or
go anywhere tomorrow morning.   They won't go
.   We went too far
.  [Music]
Hi
hi,
what's up with the sudden hug?
Shopping?
Who are
you?
Warning.
Warning?
Me too, oh my god.   The
elevator has to stop halfway.
We thought it would be good to do something.  This guy is
like an apple.  It's
like a straight line.
Oh, he's looking at us.  [Sigh] My
breath is coming in heavily.  Muruga  If
you
've done something wrong to me, that's a safety
net.
Isn't this a bit too much for you?
How can you think we're so wrong?  Is it
wrong for us to think of you this way?   Will
we have black too?
How do you know I misunderstood you?
All the details I know, all the girls and
boys think like this.   The
elevator was stopped right before my eyes. The
mechanic said, "The
elevator is
stopped. Are you playing?
Play.
Will it be another hour?
Or will it be another 10 or 15 minutes?" I
asked, "Will it be another hour?" We made it
one hour.  It'll
be one hour, if that's how
long it takes to suffocate and die,
that's fine too. There's no
problem, no cell phone bill,
no electricity bill, no house rent
.  I don't even need to go shopping.  This eyebrow
pencil doesn't need any lipstick.
I don't wear any makeup.  I just
washed my face and put on some lipstick
.
What is this?
It's just that the cream
moonshine works, everything else is the same
.   Do
you love someone?
You haven't
seen anyone with the qualities I think they have yet.
How should I be?
You must have read a lot.  You have to have a big job and
be very, very good.   If I
only got that foreigner in my hands,
I would have
congratulated you.
We don't have any ideas on what kind of food you should make,
because they have
a taste for what they say.  It's hard because of the girls
.   I left the
elevator ready and
turned on due to bad habits.
Hey,
hey, I've already been beaten by you, so
now I have to go down to the elevator and find
Tamar.   That
's it,
that's it
[music]
[sighing][breathing] You guys
are singing, I'm
suspicious again, I'm angry, I'm leaving, don't be angry,
why do I feel so wrong, okay, okay, okay,
how did you shake it
?   Are
you okay now?
Okay now.
[Music]
Okay, buy it.
Okay.   Okay, no
.
Okay, okay.
Lift.
I still have three flavors of that hair spray.
This is the best.  Turn it on quickly,
hey, put it on like that, put it on [music], put it on